DEDEN KURNIA

Tangerang, 03 - 05 - 1995
Panunggangan Utara, Tangerang
dedenkurnia001@gmail.com
089663758497

Summary

I am an bachelor information system who has some work experience as an IT support position. I can operate software, hardware well, developer website, network installation. I have integrity, able to adapt at company, hard worker, and initiative.

Skill Highlights

- Microsoft Office
- PHP Developer
- Wordpress Developer
- Network Installation
- Software & Hardware Installation

Experience

IT Staff - 07/2019 to 01/2021

PT. Putra Mustika Prima (MPM Parts)

- Maintenance hardware.
- Troubleshoot hardware software user.
- Monitoring network.
- Asset management IT.
- Inventory management (Microsoft Dynamic AX)

IT Support - 01/2021 to 02/2021

Pasifik group internasional

- Web developer (company profile).
- Graphic design.

IT Admin - 03/2021 to 12/2022

PT. Karya citra cemerlang (KCC)

- Entry data.
- Monitoring stock.
- Troubleshoot hardware software user.

IT Support - 01/2023 to Now

PT INDO TAICHEN TEXTILE INDUSTRY

- Monitoring stock.
- Troubleshoot hardware & software user.
- Instalasi jaringan LAN
- Instalasi haringan CCTV

Education

Bachelor of Computer: Sistem Informasi (2013 – 2018)

Universitas Raharja

Vocational High School: **Software Engineering (2010 – 2013)**

SMKN 5 Tangerang